export const affiliateData = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question: "How do I become an affiliate with ExpertSkillz?",
    answer:
      'To become an affiliate with ExpertSkillz, simply click on the "Get Started" button on the homepage. When you reach the registration page, choose the option to register as an affiliate and provide the necessary details distinct from those used for student registration.',
    open: false,
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "How often do affiliates get paid?",
    answer:
      "Affiliates receive payments every week for their affiliate commissions.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "In what currency are affiliate payments made?",
    answer:
      "Affiliate payments are made in US dollars (USD). However, affiliates can withdraw their earnings to their local currency.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Do affiliates need to pay anything to get started?",
    answer:
      "No, ExpertSkillz provides all the necessary resources and tools for affiliates to begin their affiliate activities without any upfront costs.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What support is available for affiliates?",
    answer:
      "ExpertSkillz offers dedicated support to affiliates, assisting them with any questions or issues they may encounter during their affiliate journey.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Can affiliates track their earnings and performance?",
    answer:
      "Yes, affiliates have access to a dashboard where they can track their earnings, performance metrics, and other relevant data in real-time.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Are there any minimum requirements to become an affiliate?",
    answer:
      "There are no specific minimum requirements to become an affiliate with ExpertSkillz. We welcome individuals from all backgrounds and levels of experience to join our affiliate program.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "How can affiliates promote ExpertSkillz courses?",
    answer:
      "Affiliates are provided with various marketing materials, including flyers, and promotional content, to effectively promote ExpertSkillz courses to their audience.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "When do affiliates get paid?",
    answer:
      "Affiliates can withdraw their earnings every Saturday, the only day designated for withdrawals. Once withdrawn, funds are allocated to your local bank account on Sunday.",
    open: false,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "How can affiliates contact support for assistance?",
    answer:
      "Affiliates can reach out to our support team via email or through the support portal for any inquiries or assistance needed regarding their affiliate activities.",
    open: false,
  },
];
